[
  {
    "question": "What year was Rockhurst high school founded?",
    "correct_answer": "1910",
    "incorrect_answers": ["1898", "1901", "1925"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Rockhurst students participate in varsity sports?",
    "correct_answer": "583",
    "incorrect_answers": ["245", "528", "490"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many service hours does the Rockhurst student body donate annually?",
    "correct_answer": "40,000 hours",
    "incorrect_answers": ["25,000 hours", "47,000 hours", "59,000 hours"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many varsity sports does Rockhurst offer?",
    "correct_answer": "11",
    "incorrect_answers": ["13", "7", "9"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many state championships does the Rockhurst tennis team have?",
    "correct_answer": "11",
    "incorrect_answers": ["7", "9", "6"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many STEAM-based courses does Rockhurst offer?",
    "correct_answer": "14",
    "incorrect_answers": ["12", "10", "8"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many consecutive state titles has the Rockhurst swim & dive team win?",
    "correct_answer": "11",
    "incorrect_answers": ["12", "5", "6"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many ZIP codes are represented at the Rock?",
    "correct_answer": "95",
    "incorrect_answers": ["102", "86", "72"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What year did Rockhurst move to its current location on State Line Road?",
    "correct_answer": "1962",
    "incorrect_answers": ["1952", "1940", "1969"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is not a student publication at Rockhurst?",
    "correct_answer": "the Hawklet Press",
    "incorrect_answers": ["the Prep News", "the Quarry", "The Rock Collection"]
  }
]
